Testing with URL from file: https://www.ted.com/talks/yi_li_the_missing_piece_in_climate_action_it_s_not_what_you_think
Status: 200
Title: The missing piece in climate action (it&apos;s not what you think)
Blocks Count: 1
Blocks Count: 1
First Block Content Preview:
3,000 farmers supported. Six million dollars in direct income to farmers. 50 tons of food waste prevented every month. These numbers represent FarmWorks鈥檚 impact over the last five years. But what if I tell you they are no longer the most important metrics to me anymore? Today, the number one metric that I care about as CEO of FarmWorks is our profitability. Now before you judge me and think, &quot;How did we let this capitalist on the stage?&quot; hear me out. Five years ago, I cofounded FarmWo
